# JESSIE COLEMAN

Decatur GA · (915) 831 9109 Jessiecoleman928@gmail.com

Upcoming fourth year student at Emory University. Experienced with working with Agile/Scrum as well as OpenAl Api, React JS, OOP programming, web design, app design, and game development.

# **EXPERIENCE**

JUN 2023 - PRESENT

### **SWE INTERN PUBLICIS SAPIENT**

Frontend/backend software engineer intern for popular retail corporation. Used React JS as well as ChatGPT API.

**AUG 2022 - PRESENT** 

#### **EMORY COMPUTER SCIENCE LAB STAFF**

My responsibilities include tutoring computer science students, computer repair, and computer maintenance.

MAY 2022 - AUG 2022

#### **BEST BUY COMPUTER REPAIR**

My job was to diagnose and fix software/hardware problems with clients' computers, as well as smartphones and tablets.

# **EDUCATION**

**MAY 2019** 

HIGH SCHOOL DIPLOMA, FRANKLIN HIGH SCHOOL

**JUNE 2020-PRESENT** 

**COMPUTER SCIENCE, EMORY UNIVERSITY** 

# **SKILLS**

- Java/C#/C
- HTML/CSS/JavaScript

- Python/Lua
- Unity/Android Studio/Arduino
- React JS/OpenAl API

# **PROJECTS**

- Created online multiplayer tank game https://sacredstudios.itch.io/chidi-tanks-03-alpha
- Created visualization of A\* pathfinding algorithm using Arduino.
- Created website using CSS/JavaScript/HTML.
- Created map/sprites for 2D game with Unity
- Created generative math quiz using ChatGPT and React JS.
- Created animated poster using Android Studio.